Diwali has come, listen dear one,
now he has become the enemy,
now the enemy is
showing his rights
[Music]
Yes brother, how did you like it
Wait, be patient.   It's
bad right now brother.  It's bad right now.
But what is this guy doing here?
Hey Baba
[Music]
Now you are gone son, now you are gone, look here
Prannath, take the Fuljhari weapon, here you are
Swami,
oh [ __ ] friend, wow, what a smile,
so much happiness, what happened
?
Prannath, all the weapons of the enemies have been destroyed.
Take this item bomb weapon and destroy them completely.
That very night,
that too got closed.  I am facing such a problem.
Death stands in our path.
But one second.
Happy Diwali
Happy Diwali Wale